National Railroad Adjustment Board Case Files 5837
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Award No. 1626. Docket No. 1536. Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Co. MR Jackson., 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Award No. 1628. Docket No. 1557. Florida East Coast Railway Co. LE Short., 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Award No. 1629. Docket No. 1560. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. Caswell Garber., 1959-1962 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Award No. 1630. Docket No. 1561. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. Tom Barrett., 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Award No. 1631. Docket No. 1564. Erie Railroad. RJ Bishop and MF Dailey., 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Award No. 1632. Docket No. 1570. Long Island Railroad Co. ED Lawrence., 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Award No. 1636. Docket No. 1598. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. Le Walsh., 1962 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Award No. 1637. Docket No. 1600. Missouri Pacific Railroad. MJ Walters., 1960-1963 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Award No. 1643. Docket No. 1747. Chicago and North Western Railway Co. WH Allonge., 1961-1962 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Award No. 1647. Docket No. 1761. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. ME Wendell., 1961-1962 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Award No. 1648. Docket No. 1762. Lehigh Valley Railroad. ME Wendell., 1962 (Box 60, Folder 18)
- Award No. 1651. Docket No. 1476. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. JT Landry., 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Award No. 1652. Docket No. 1540. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific Railroad. Landry and Peterson., 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Award No. 1214. Docket No. 3270. Chicago and North Western Railway Co. Pay Claims., 1958 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Chicago North Western Documents., 1957-1958 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- Award No. 1653. Docket No. 1563. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. Landry and Peterson., 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 23)
- Award No. 1656. Docket No. 1602. Union Pacific Railroad. Los Angeles, California., 1946-1961 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Award No. 1657. Docket No. 1624. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. Various Yardmasters., 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 25)
- Award No. 1299. Docket No. 1279. Chicago and North Western. HM Palm and DF Janzen., 1957-1958 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Award No. 1301. Docket No. 1287. Chicago and North Western Case. R Stavlo., 1958 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Award No. 1302. Docket No. 1308. JL Eberts., 1957-1958 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Award No. 1303. Docket No. 1309. Grand Trunk Western Railroad. RT McDonald., 1958 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Award No. 1306. Docket No. 1372. Baltimore and Ohio. M Urbania., 1958 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Award No. 1310. Docket No. 1356. Chicago and North Western. DO McDonald., 1958 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Award No. 1311. Docket No. 1362. Chicago and North Western. EL Briley and JL Ebert., 1958 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Award No. 1312. Docket No. 1363. Chicago and North Western Railway. CR Gainey., 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Award No. 1313. Docket No. 1364. Chicago and North Western. HE Meier., 1957-1959 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Award No. 1314. Docket No. 1390. Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Co. CB Beauregard., 1958 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Award No. 1315. Docket No. 1391. Denver and Rio Grande Western. PH Whitcomb., 1958 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Award No. 1316. Docket No. 1392. Denver Rio Grande Western Railroad Co. PH Whitcomb., 1958 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Award No. 1319. Docket No. 1228. Terminal Railroad Association. Yardmaster Pay., 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Award No. 1320. Docket No. 1227. Terminal Railroad Association. Yardmaster Pay., 1956-1958 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Award No. 1321. Docket No. 1272. Terminal Railroad Association. JE Brooks., 1957-1958 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Award No. 1322. Docket No. 1273. Terminal Railroad Association. HL Toothaker., 1957-1958 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Award No. 1323. Docket No. 1274. Terminal Railroad Association. Claim for Oldest Extra Yardmaster., 1957-1958 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Award No. 1324. Docket No. 1275. Terminal Railroad Association. Oldest Unassigned Extra Man., 1957-1958 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- Award No. 1325. Docket No. 1276. Terminal Railroad Association. Oldest Unassigned Man., 1958 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- Award No. 1326. Docket No. 1277. Terminal Railroad Association. Oldest Unassigned Extra Man., 1957-1958 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Award No. 1327. Docket No. 1278. Terminal Railroad Association. Unassigned Yardmasters., 1957-1958 (Box 61, Folder 21)
- Award No. 1334. Docket No. 1398. Chicago and North Western. Milwaukee Claims. Swan et al., 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 22)
- Award No. 1335. Docket No. 1383. Southern Railway System. Oldest Available Yardmasters., 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 23)
- Award No. 1338. Docket No. 1428. Chicago and North Western. Milwaukee Claims., 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Award No. 1340. Docket No. 1319. Northern Pacific Railway. AW Henry., 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 25)
- Communication., 1958 (Box 61, Folder 26)
- Award No. 1343. Docket No. 1324. Missouri Pacific Railroad. JA Stanley., 1957-1959 (Box 61, Folder 27)
- Award No. 1356. Docket No. 1425. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co. CE Carmical Case., 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 28)
- Award No. 1361. Docket No. 1350. Chicago and North Western Railway Co. RR Gregg., 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 29)
- Award No. 1362. Docket No. 1352. Chicago and North Western. WJ Swan., 1958 (Box 61, Folder 30)
- Docket No. 745. Award No. 752. Minnesota Transfer Railway Co. NH Alexander., 1951 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Docket No. 748. Award No. 754. Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Co. Jacksonville, Florida., 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Docket No. 755. Award No. 759. Boston and Maine. CE Wright., 1951 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Docket No. 789. Award No. 760. Santa Fe. AA Bales, Argentine, Kansas., 1950-1952 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Docket No. 807. Award No. 761. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Co. West Yard., 1952 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Docket No. 808. Award No. 762. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Ivan Haworth., 1952 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Docket No. 756. Award No. 766. Seaboard Airline Railroad Co. WH McGowan., 1952 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Docket No. 757. Award No. 767. Seaboard Air Line Railroad Co. Miami, Florida., 1950-1952 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Docket No. 758. Docket No. 768. Seaboard Air Line Railroad Co. Charleston, South Carolina., 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Docket No. 769. Award No. 759. Seaboard Air Line Railroad Co. Brown St Yard, Richmond Terminal, Virginia., 1950-1952 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Docket No. 766. Award No. 775. Southern Pacific. FS Alexander and WW Clark., 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Docket No. 767. Award No. 776. Chesapeake and Ohio. FN Hutchins., 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Docket No. 771. Award No. 779. Pennsylvania Railroad. EP Kraus. GC Dermatatis., 1951-1954 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Docket No. 819. Award No. 785. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. EJ Benton., 1952 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Docket No. 838. Award No. 786. Chicago Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Co. RD Connors., 1952 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Docket No. 780. Award No. 788. Great Northern. E LaMere., 1951 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Docket No. 783. Award No. 789. St Louis and San Francisco. TB Horan., 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Docket No. 785. Award No. 790. Southern Pacific Co. Pacific Lines. AR Talley., 1953 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- Docket No. 791. Award No. 791. Santa Fe. JW Hanner., 1950-1952 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- Docket No. 805. Award No. 792. Gulf, Mobile and Ohio. AE Bridie., 1952 (Box 62, Folder 20)
- Docket No. 806. Award No. 793. St Louis-San Francisco Railroad. CE Campbell., 1952 (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Docket No. 813. Award No. 797. St Louis-San Francisco Railway Co., 1952 (Box 62, Folder 22)
- Docket No. 817. Award No. 799. Missouri Pacific. WL Faulk, HE Hussey, ED Smith., 1952 (Box 62, Folder 23)
- Docket No. 784. Award No. 802. Terminal railroad Association of St Louis. Union Station., 1951-1953 (Box 62, Folder 24)
- Docket No. 786. Award No. 802. Southern Pacific Co. Pacific Lines. C Miller., 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 25)
- Docket No. 787. Award No. 803. Southern Pacific Co. Pacific Lines. GJ Carston., 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 26)
- Docket No. 696. Award No. 699. Union Pacific. OE Vallen. Seattle, Washington., 1950-1951 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Docket No. 697. Award No. 700. Ogden Union Railway and Depot Co. EL Mumford., 1950-1951 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Docket No. 714. Award No. 714. Port Terminal. CG Schwarz., 1951 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Docket No. 716. Award No. 715. Southern Pacific. Chevrolet Yard., 1951 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Docket No. 717. Award No. 716. Southern Pacific. Stockton Yard, Stockton, California., 1950-1951 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Docket No. 718. Award No. 717. Southern Pacific. Homestead Yard., 1950-1951 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Docket No. 720. Award No. 719. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy. EE Walker. Pacific Junction., 1951 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Docket No. 723. Award No. 722. Chesapeake and Ohio. Marion, Ohio., 1951 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Docket No. 724. Award No. 723. Baltimore and Ohio. RW Cover., 1951 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Docket No. 734. Award No. 724. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. RW Cover., 1951 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Docket No. 725. Award No. 729. Southern Pacific. Oakland, California., 1848-1951 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Docket No. 726. Award No. 730. Southern Pacific. Oakland, California., 1951 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Docket No. 729. Award No. 731. Baltimore and Ohio. JG Copp., 1951 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Docket No. 731. Award No. 732. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. EL Klaus. Pittsburgh Terminal., 1950-1951 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Docket No. 730. Award No. 733. Florida East Coast. DO Fox., 1950 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Docket No. 732. Award No. 734. St Louis - San Francisco. ME Brinkman. North La Crosse, Wisconsin., 1951-1952 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Docket No. 737. Award No. 737. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad. MG Harper. Chicago, Illinois., 1950-1951 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Docket No. 739. Award No. 739. St Louis - San Francisco. Madison St Yard, Midcontinent Yard., 1951-1952 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Award No. 2245. Docket No. 2221. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. RL Barnes, GL Berry, CH Englebrecht, HR Reed., 1965-1967 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Award No. 2246. Docket No. 2222. Grand Trunk Western. RA Luotonen., 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Award No. 2250. Docket No. 2332. Norfolk and Western. JD Schepis., 1967 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Award No. 2251. Docket No. 2333. Norfolk and Western. DC Seipel., 1967 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Award No. 2253. Docket No. 2204. Grand Trunk Western. Kalamazoo, Michigan. NF Myers., 1966-1968 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Award No. 2254. Docket No. 2207. Terminal Railroad Association of St Louis. CA Waters., 1966-1968 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Award No. 2256. Docket No. 2211. Union Pacific Railroad. DE Gardner., 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Award No. 2257. Docket No. 2223. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Co. PC Kovacs., 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Award No. 2255. Docket No. 2212. Union Pacific Railroad. Milton Thomas., 1965-1968 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Award No. 2197. Docket No. 2177. Pennsylvania Railroad. YM -254. TH Bainbridge., 1966 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Award No. 2206. Docket No. 2229. Norfolk and Western. WM Andrews., 1967 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Soo Line Railroad Co. Civil Action No. 69-C-82. Docket No. 2160., 1945-1970 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Award No. 2207. Docket No. 2235. Grand Trunk Western. DP Jones., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Award No. 2209. Docket No. 2276. Pennsylvania Railroad Co. SG Brake., 1967 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Award No. 2210. Docket No. 2178. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. RJ Culver., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Award No. 2211. Docket No. 2179. Lehigh Valley Railroad. WJ Donovan., 1965-1967 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Award No. 2213. Docket No. 2189. Lehigh Valley Railroad. W Minnich., 1966 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Award No. 2214. Docket No. 2190. Lehigh Valley Railroad. Charles J Toth., 1966 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Award No. 2215. Docket No. 2191. Lehigh Valley Railroad. Marvin Wendell., 1966 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Award No. 2216. Docket No. 2192. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy. Don F Milgrim., 1966-1969 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Award No. 2217. Docket No. 2188. Union Pacific Railroad. Glenn M Franke., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Award No. 2218. Docket No. 2196. Erie-Lackawanna. AT Fagan and PA Acquino., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Award No. 2220. Docket No. 2199. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. LJ Smith., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Award No. 2221. Docket No. 2208. Chicago, Milwaukee, St Paul and Pacific. WM Snyder and LJ Smith., 1965-1967 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Award No. 2222. Docket No. 2200. Chicago and North Western Railway. RJ Morris., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- Award No. 2223. Docket No. 2201. Norfolk and Western. JJ Rudnick., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Award No. 2225. Docket No. 2197. Buffalo Creek Railroad. DJ Hayes., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 18)
- Award No. 2228. Docket No. 2299. Washington Terminal. Hiram Cornett., 1967 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- Award No. 2233. Docket No. 2331. Norfolk and Western. EL Kister., 1967 (Box 65, Folder 20)
- Award No. 2234. Docket No. 2195. Minnesota Transfer. JA Mullen., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- Award No. 2235. Docket No. 2205. Grand Trunk Western. CL Norton., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 22)
- Award No. 2236. Docket No. 2206. Grand Trunk Western. WN Roddy., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 23)
- Award No. 2237. Docket No. 2210. Grand Trunk Western. RA Luotonen., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 24)
- Award No. 2238. Docket No. 2213. Pennsylvania Railroad. Western Region. System Docket 170. Chicago Division Case C-41-65., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 25)
- Award No. 2240. Docket No. 2216. Pennsylvania Railroad. LW Holleran., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 26)
- Award No. 2241. Docket No. 2217. Pennsylvania Railroad Co. Strubel., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 27)
- Award No. 2244. Docket No. 2220. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. TH Johnson., 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 28)
- Award No. 1042. Docket No. 1035. Southern Pacific Co. Yardmaster Position One., 1954-1955 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Award No. 1531. Docket No. 1578. Southern Pacific Co. Pay for Senior Qualified Yardmasters., 1961 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Award No. 1996. Docket No. 1965. Southern Pacific Co. FA Drake., 1964-1965 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Docket No. 9805. Awards No. 9805, 9534, 9529. Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad., 1943-1949 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Award No. 12539. Docket No. 9053. St Paul Union Depot Co., 1932-1935 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Award No. 7106. Docket No. 9363. Chicago Rock Island and Pacific Railway Co. John Benson., 1927-1940 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Award No. 6585. Docket No. 12593. New York Central Railroad Co. Yardmen's Seniority Right to Service., 1941 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Award No. 7110. Docket No. 13533. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. JJ Rowe and MD Oldfather., 1941 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Award No. 8101. Docket No. 15809. Sioux City Terminal Railroad. Pryor., 1942 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Award No. 12380. Docket No. 16473. Western Pacific., 1949 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Award No. 13143. Docket No. 17208. Western Pacific Railroad Co. JL Nichols., 1943-1949 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Award No. 9801. Docket No. 18126. The Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Co. AC McCall et al., 1943-1944 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Award No. 9526. Docket No. 18131. Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Co. JB Warner and JL Langston., 1944 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Award No. 9528. Docket No. 18239. Salt Lake City Union Depot. GJ Rhea., 1944 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Award No. 11943. Docket No. 19342. Public Belt Railroad Commission of New Orleans. JF Fitzpatrick., 1944-1948 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Docket No. 19825. Chicago, Milwaukee St Paul - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy., 1951-1953 (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Award No. 13233. Docket No. 19825. Davenport, Rock Island and North Western Railway. Minimum Day's Pay., 1942-1950 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- Docket No. 20346. The Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Co. FF Weisser et al., 1944 (Box 66, Folder 18)
- Award No. 11555. Docket No. 21404. The Western pacific railroad Co. JC Gwaltney, et al., 1945 (Box 66, Folder 19)
- Award No. 11733. Docket No. 21605. Western Pacific Railroad Co. Rudolph Sniersek., 1945-1946 (Box 66, Folder 20)
- Award No. 11735. Docket No. 21607. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway Co. Claim for Eight Hours., 1946 (Box 66, Folder 21)
- Award No. 13277. Docket No. 21659. Oakland Terminal. WH Clouette., 1946-1950 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- Award No. 13322. Docket No. 22031. The Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Co. ED Burleigh., 1947 (Box 66, Folder 23)
- Award No. 13323. Docket No. 22334. The Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Co. CC Sims et al., 1947-1950 (Box 66, Folder 24)
- Award No. 12421. Docket No. 22355. Union Railway. EL Burkholder, Indianapolis., 1945-1949 (Box 66, Folder 25)
- Award No. 23100. Docket No. 15078. Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer. AL Marx., 1948 (Box 66, Folder 26)
- Award No. 23383-384. Western Pacific. 14415-14416., 1948-1951 (Box 66, Folder 27)
- Award No. 23407. Docket No. 15081. Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer Railway Co. AL Marx et al., 1948-1952 (Box 66, Folder 28)
- Award No. 15054. Docket No. 23900. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Co. Ned J Brodt., 1949-1952 (Box 66, Folder 29)
- Award No. 15300. Docket No. 23919. Award No. 14993. Docket No. 23920. Minneapolis and St Louis., 1948-1952 (Box 66, Folder 30)
- Award No. 15433. Docket No. 24408. Western Pacific Railroad Co. Jesse Barnett., 1947-1949 (Box 66, Folder 31)
- Award No. 15487. Docket No. 24420. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. JF White, Paul E Reber et al., 1934-1946 (Box 66, Folder 32)
- Award No. 16441. Docket No. 24448. Buffalo Creek Railroad. Senior Unplaced Switchmen., 1946-1949 (Box 66, Folder 33)
- Award No. 15611. Docket No. 24492. Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad Co. RA Carroll., 1949-1950 (Box 66, Folder 34)
- Award No. 15600. Docket No. 24523. Great Northern Railway Co., 1947-1949 (Box 66, Folder 35)
- Award No. 15500-15501. Docket No. 24524-24526. Great Northern Railway Co. JM Creighton., 1946 (Box 66, Folder 36)
- Award No. 15847. Docket No. 24649. Great Northern Railway Co. RK Halley., 1949 (Box 66, Folder 37)
- Award No. 15848. Docket No. 24650. Great Northern Railway Co. B Davis, HD Barret and HJ Morrow., 1948-1952 (Box 66, Folder 38)
- Award No. 16520. Docket No. 24664. Indianapolis Unio Railway. Additional Pay., 1949-1953 (Box 66, Folder 39)
- Award No. 15714. Docket No. 24742. Great Northern Railway Co. George Blair et al., 1949-1952 (Box 66, Folder 40)
- Award No. 15761. Docket No. 24835. Northern Pacific Terminal Co of Oregon. CR Phillips., 1949 (Box 66, Folder 41)
- Award No. 15789. Docket No. 24900. Great Northern Railway. KR Stroh., 1949 (Box 66, Folder 42)
- Award No. 15899, 15856. Docket No. 25247-25148. Great Northern Railway. WA Williams et al., 1947 (Box 66, Folder 43)
- Award No. 15791. Docket No. 25078. Northern Pacific Terminal Co of Oregon. GC Hague., 1949 (Box 66, Folder 44)
- Award No. 16380. Docket No. 25186. Denver Lackawanna and Western. Edward Harkins et al., 1935-1952 (Box 66, Folder 45)
- Award No. 16087. Docket No. 25364. Western Pacific Railroad. SF Dorius., 1949 (Box 66, Folder 46)
- Award No. 14406. Docket No. 25435. Sacramento Northern Railway. CE George., 1949 (Box 66, Folder 47)
- Award No. 16090-16092. Docket No. 25479-25482. Great Northern Railway Co. Baker, Spindler, Forsgreen, PM Bates., 1948 (Box 66, Folder 48)
- Award No. 16094. Docket No. 25506. Northern Pacific Terminal Railroad. EE Pence et al., 1949 (Box 66, Folder 49)
- Award No. 15897. Docket No. 25532. Southern Pacific Co. JH Heady., 1949 (Box 66, Folder 50)
- Award No. 15897. Docket No. 25532. Southern Pacific Co. JH Heady., 1948-1952 (Box 66, Folder 51)
- Award No. 16140. Docket No. 25549. Great Northern Railway Co. Sam Fox et al., 1950 (Box 66, Folder 52)
- Award No. 18506. Docket No. 33006. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. Francis L Watson., 1955-1957 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Docket No. 3304. Award No. 18507. Southern Pacific. PJ Burke, JH Heady and DD Phelps., 1950-1957 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Docket No. 33077. Award No. 18575. Southern Pacific Co. RR Ware., 1955-1958 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Docket No. 33108. Award No. 18574. Southern Pacific Co. Hall and Ware., 1958 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Docket No. 33158. Award No. 18578. Southern Pacific. Engine Foreman May and June., 1955-1958 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Docket No. 33167. Award No. 18579. Southern Pacific. Dunsmuir Yard., 1954-1958 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Docket No. 33183. Award No. 18678. Southern Pacific. Claims., 1954-1958 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Docket No. 33203. Award No. 18679. Northern Pacific Terminal Co of Oregon. Fred Ludwig., 1955-1958 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Docket No. 33203. Award No. 18679. Northern Pacific Terminal Co of Oregon. Fred Ludwig., 1958 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Docket No. 33151. Award No. 18312. Chicago Rock Island and Pacific. Donahoe, Hitchcock, Moran., 1957 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Docket No. 33161. Award No. 18580. Chicago Rock Island and Pacific. JB Parker., 1955-1958 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Docket No. 33204. Award No. 18657. Southern Pacific. JA Brown, BR Williams, WB With., 1953-1958 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Docket No. 33211. Award No. 18684. Southern Pacific. Senior Yardman., 1955-1958 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Docket No. 33219. Award No. 18685. Southern Pacific. Davis, Wilkins., 1942-1958 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Docket No. 33229. Award No. 18686. Southern Pacific Co. CE Peacock., 1955-1958 (Box 67, Folder 15)
- Docket No. 33240. Award No. 18703. Southern Pacific. Yard Helpers., 1951-1958 (Box 67, Folder 16)
- Docket No. 33282. Award No. 17454. Southern Pacific. PW DeVore., 1953-1955 (Box 67, Folder 17)
- Docket No. 33292. Award No. 18704. Southern Pacific. Dunsmuir Extra Board., 1955-1958 (Box 67, Folder 18)
- Docket No. 33325. Award No. 18658. Southern Pacific. WE Roe., 1954-1958 (Box 67, Folder 19)
- Docket No. 33326. Award No. 18705. Southern Pacific Co. Martinsen, Mayfield, Jacobson., 1955-1958 (Box 67, Folder 20)
- Docket No. 33351. Award No. 18696. Southern Pacific. HA Bartnik, Justice Shay., 1954-1958 (Box 67, Folder 21)
- Docket No. 33399. Award No. 18669. Southern Pacific Co. CL McCool., 1953-1955 (Box 67, Folder 22)
- Docket No. 33424. Award No. 18865. Southern Pacific Co. HG Hayes et al., 1955-1959 (Box 67, Folder 23)
- Docket No. 33425. Award No. 18894. Southern Pacific Co. DE Lucas et al., 1955 (Box 67, Folder 24)
- Docket No. 33429. Award No. 17645. Southern Pacific. John N Stephens., 1955 (Box 67, Folder 25)
- Docket No. 33478. Award No. 18895. Southern Pacific. CH Miller., 1955-1956 (Box 67, Folder 26)
- Docket No. 33529. Award No. 18830. Southern Pacific. RA Taylor et al., 1956-1958 (Box 67, Folder 27)
- Docket No. 33572. Award No. 18634. Southern Pacific. JH Heady et al., 1956-1958 (Box 67, Folder 28)
- Docket No. 33591. Award No. 18831. Los Angeles Junction Railway Co. Kyle Harrell., 1956-1958 (Box 67, Folder 29)
- Docket No. 33644. Award No. 18832. Los Angeles Junction Railway. Benge, Kemmer, Rippy., 1956-1958 (Box 67, Folder 30)
- Docket No. 33649. Award No. 18833. Southern Pacific. Kasner, Bryant, Carroll., 1955-1958 (Box 67, Folder 31)
- Docket No. 33650. Award No. 18834. Southern Pacific. Martinsen, Hougak, Orthmeyer., 1958 (Box 67, Folder 32)
- Docket No. 33651. Award No. 18835. Southern Pacific. Wright, Hays van Buren., 1955-1958 (Box 67, Folder 33)
- Docket No. 33706. Award No. 17486. Southern Pacific. R Rodrgues., 1945-1956 (Box 67, Folder 34)
- Docket No. 33763. Award No. 17588. Southern Pacific. RD Colyer., 1945-1956 (Box 67, Folder 35)
- Docket No. 33789. Award No. 18872. Southern Pacific. Grayson., 1956 (Box 67, Folder 36)
- Docket No. 33660. Award No. 18857. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. DJ Felton et al., 1958 (Box 67, Folder 37)
- Docket No. 33673. Award No. 18858. Southern Pacific. Wilkerson, Phillips and Garner., 1956-1958 (Box 67, Folder 38)